

Pattarapol Leemeechoke

Multidisciplinary designer

- Graphic design
- Illustration
- Motion work

Nationality Thai

Location Osaka, Japan

Contact daftput@gmail.com

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/daftput

Portfolio https://daftput.github.io/ portfolio/index.html

I'm a multidisciplinary designer currently based in Osaka, originally from Bangkok. With a total of 7 years of experience in professional environments and various freelance projects with companies and local businesses. I am specialized in creating digital media, print and merchandise designs, utilizing my diverse background in industrial design and graphic design, as well as my personal interest in illustration and innovations in both industrial and automotive field.

My approach to design emphasizes the design process and collaborative works, I ensure each work delivers on both creativity and create meaningful solutions, Striving to achieve the best outcome that meets the client and project goals and objectives

Experience

DAFTPUT | Freelance design service

Mar 2017 - Present

Freelance design services, providing creative solutions to graphic designs, illustrations and motion works and other creative ventures.

- Collaborative work with clients to achieve the most meaningful solutions that meets the criteria.
- Providing creative solutions to clients to ensure the quality of the outcome of each projects.

Gentle Underground Monkeys co.ltd | Full-time in-house designer Apr 2021 - Mar 2024

In-house designer in a creative company that runs both independent film production and restaurant management business. Focusing on producing new concepts of films and businesses.

Collaborative involvement in motion media projects from pre-production to post-production process.

- Design Logos, poster, flyers and other promotional materials both digital and tangible.
- Worked on intros and openings, insert-animation and other video editing and visual designs in motion media projects.
- Merchandise planning and production.
- Desktop Publishing (DTP) Coordinator.

Branding and identity for involved businesses under the company's management.

- Design Logos, poster, flyers and other promotional materials both digital and tangible that fits each business's image and identity.
- Social media promotional content designs collaborated with the company team.
- Merchandise planning and production.
- Desktop Publishing (DTP) Coordinator.



Pattarapol Leemeechoke

Multidisciplinary designer

- · Graphic design
- Illustration
- Motion work

Nationality Thai

Location Osaka, Japan

Contact daftput@gmail.com

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/daftput

Portfolio

https://daftput.github.io/ portfolio/index.html

Skills

Graphic design

Logo design, Graphic art, Poster design, Flyer design, Typography.

Illustration

Illustrative design, Editorial Illustration, Illustration based visuals and graphics.

Motion work

Video editing, Motion graphics, 2D Animation, Pixel Animation.

Design Tools

Adobe Creative Suite

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Lightroom Adobe Aftereffects Adobe Premier Pro, Adobe Dimension

Finalcut Pro X

Video Editng

Procreate

Digital Illustration

Pixaki

Pixel art & Animation

Figma

UX/UI Design & Prototyping

Education

Osaka Designer Academy | Graphic design Department

Apr 2019 - Mar 2021

Technical Diploma(Graphic design)

Seigan Japanese Language School

April 2017 - March 2019

Certificate of Completion(Japanese studies)

King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi | SoA+D

June 2011 - Nov 2016

Bachelor of Fine and Applied arts(Industrial design)

Languages

Thai

Native

English

Full Professional

Japanese

Professional Working

Certification

JLPT Japanese-Language Proficiency Test

Score: N2 · Jul 2019

Private Car Driving License(Thailand)

Issue date : Aug 2012

IELTS(Academic) Test

Score: 6.0 · Feb 2011